> > Brian Holt: 到目前为止我们谈论的是 JustReact，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
far we've been talking about JustReact,
你永远不会看到有人利用朱斯特雷法对吧
and you'll never see anyone
using JustReact, right?
就像我们一直在做的那样，这并不是一个非常普遍的模式
Like we've been doing so far,
that's just not a very common pattern for
写 React ，总是有工具的，对吧 ?
writing React,
there's always tools involve, right?
这也是我的方法，我也来自前端的基础设施。
And that again, my methodology, and I come
from front end infrastructure as well.
所以我要去做我疯狂的人
So I'm going to subject to my madness,
is that you need to
除了了解框架外，还了解您的工具。
understand your tools in addition to
just understanding the framework.
所以我尽量保持尽量轻但我还是会帮你
So, I'm gonna keep as light as possible,
but I'm going to still help you
理解我的意见中的一些更有效的写作方法
understand some of the better ways
to write React in my opinion.
我们要把你介绍给你三四个工具
So, here we're gonna introduce you
to like, three or four tools, and
那我们就能回去写雷法了
then we'll get back to writing React.
所以我想给你介绍的第一个，你可能已经熟悉了 NPM。
So the first one I wanna introduce you to,
you may already be familiar with is NPM.
这不代表节点软件包管理器，但代表了
Which does not stand for node package
manager, but sort of stands for
节点软件包管理器。
node package manager.
>> Brian Holt: 这将允许我们，而不是仅将节点装入
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is going to allow us
to, rather than just loading node off of
CDN ，我们会把它安装在注册中心，并建造我们的项目。
the CDN, we're gonna actually install it
off of the registry and build our project.
所以它其实是包里的，
So that it's actually included
with the package, and
我们不需要依赖包裹来对吧
we don't have to rely on
unpackage to be up, right?
解包非常好，就像测试东西一样。
Unpackage is really good for
just like testing things out.
但不依赖它来生产交通，
But do not rely on it for
production traffic,
然后你就任人宰割了好吗
cuz then you're at their mercy, okay?
>> Brian Holt: 我要你做的是，我要你打开你的终端。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, what I want you to do,
is I want you to open your terminal.
这是内置的 VS 代码 ( 如果您正在使用该代码 ) 。
This is built-in the VS code,
if you are using that.
您可以打开命令，或抱歉，控制，后退，斜杠，
You can open up with command, or sorry,
control, back tick, slash tilde,
就在你的键盘旁边的那个
the one that's next to
the one on your keyboard.
>> Brian Holt: 在其他地方也有很多按钮
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's plenty of
buttons somewhere for as well but
我就是这样自己打开的好吗
that's how I was open itself, okay?
然后第一件事
And then the first thing,
您必须确保已安装节点。
you're gonna have to make sure
that you have node installed.
所以我有 10个， 15个，只要你说 8 个，
So I do, I have 10, 15, as long as
you're over like, let's say eight,
六岁的小熊被弃用了
cuz six just got deprecated.
或者说生命的终结是正确的术语。
Or end of life, rather,
is the correct term.
所以只要你在 8 岁以上就可以了
So as long as you're above eight,
you should be fine.
我在 10 . 15 岁，现在应该很接近 LTS 了。
I'm on 10.15, which should be
pretty close to the LTS right now.
你想用的就是这个
Which is the one that you wanna use.
我认为你应该使用长期支持的 LTS 。
You should use the LTS which stands for
long-term support, I think.
或者我是在说你可以相信我
Or I'm making that up and
you can believe me.
好了节点来了
Okay, so with node comes mpm,
如果您现在没有安装这些工具。
if you don't have these
tools installed right now.
只要去 nodejs.org 你也可以在那边安装就好了。
Just go to nodejs.org, and you can just
install it right after there as well.
>> Brian Holt: 因此请注意，我在桌面/采用者中
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
notice that I'm in Desktop/adopt-me, so
我在我的项目目录里
I'm inside of my project directory.
我想做的第一件事就是晚上的晚上
And the first thing that I wanna
do is I'm gonna say npm init,
这将为我创造一个新的项目
which is going to create a new project for
me.
现在我超级懒惰我不想回答任何问题
Now, I'm super lazy and
I don't wanna answer any of the questions.
所以支持提示如果你放了我就不会问你任何问题
So pro tip, if you put -y,
it won't ask you any questions and
它会为您生成一个文件。
it just generates a file for you.
否则，您会收到此交互式提示。
Otherwise you get this interactive prompt.
比如你的项目名称
Like what's the name of your project?
你是谁，什么都怪我，我就是个不烦的人。
Who are you, blah blah blah,
and I just can't be bothered.
现在，如果你看看我的项目，你可以看到我有一个 package.json。
So, now if you look at my project, you
can see here that I have a package.json.
现在，这与 JavaScript 项目很常见。
Now, this is common with
JavaScript projects.
再次，这可能不是你第一次接触这一问题。
Again, this may not be the first
time you've been exposed to this.
在这里关闭这个
Inside of here, close this.
只是一个 JSON 文件里充满了许可证的内容
It's just a JSON file full
of what the license is,
项目的名称是什么，版本是什么，等等。
what the name of the project is,
what version it is, so on and so forth.
我们真的不关心这里发生了什么
We don't actually really
care what's going on here.
如果你想的话你可以搞砸了
You can mess with it if you want to.
我不会去的
I'm not going to.
但有几件事我们会关注的
But there's a couple of things that
we're gonna be concerned with here.
首先我们要有依赖性
First one,
we're gonna have dependencies and
那些依赖性就会被跟踪到这里对吧
those dependencies are gonna
be track in here, right?
那就
So then,
每当我说 npm 安装时，就会有同样的依赖性，对吧 ?
whenever I say npm install, it's going
to grab the same dependencies, right?
所以如果我和开始一起研究一个项目，我可以向她展示一下。
So if me and Start working on a project
together, I can show this with her.
我们可以一起研究这个项目，对吧 ?
And we could work together
on that project, right?
就像这样
Something like that.